https://www.tokyoflash.com/pages/privacy-policy

FREE WORLDWIDE SHIPPING ON ALL ORDERS | EXTENDED HOLIDAY RETURNS: CONTACT US BEFORE JAN 15TH 2021
Checkout Terms
Some countries may charge tax, duties or charges on items you purchase. It is the responsibility of the recipient to pay these charges on or after delivery. Tokyoflash prices are heavily reduced to help offset any possible charges. By completing my purchase, I agree to the Tokyoflash Japan Privacy Policy.
FREE WORLDWIDE SHIPPING ON ALL ORDERS | EXTENDED HOLIDAY RETURNS: CONTACT US BEFORE JAN 15TH 2021
Watches
Watch Museum
Design Studio Blog
USD
GBP
EUR
JPY
Cart
Cart
Privacy Policy
Effective date: May 24, 2018This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.tokyoflash.com (the “Site”).SECURITYOur dedicated server uses High-Grade 256 bit SSL Encryption to protect your information. The highest level possible. To view our security certificate please click on the Padlock icon in your browser.Once you enter the Checkout page to make payment, enter the Registration page to create an account or view this Security policy page your connection to our website will become encrypted. You can verify this by checking that the URL in your browser starts with HTTPS and that you can see the Padlock icon in the corner of your browsers window.PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number. Optional information you can provide includes your fax number and company name. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfil any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you;Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; andWhen in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.DO NOT TRACKPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfil contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.DATA RETENTIONWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.MINORSThe Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 16.CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at watches@tokyoflash.com.
Welcome
Welcome to Tokyoflash Japan. Creative watch design from Japan. Made in limited production runs. Change the way you think about time.
Sign up to find out about new watch releases and special offers.
© 2020 Tokyoflash Japan.
All Rights Reserved.
